there's going to be a way to hold it back. I'm damn sure they'll probably try. But right now.
the way that I use it in my workflow. AI is good for me. It works out. I can go in there.
somebody calls me and says hey i want this AI automation of my business or i want to rank higher online whatever it is AI can do a lot of that heavy lifting because i know the inside systems
to hook it up to but even that's really not that important anymore now versus six months ago six
months ago i still had to go in there and click on the right things find the right stuff like that
that's how i did it right just like that but now i really don't have to do much of anything i can
just mention it to it so what if next week they take this away from me what happens then well i
still know how to do it however a year from now 57 what is that 60 58 yeah I might not remember
that's a problem I think we all need to pay attention to that Brad thanks gagging cakes
coach Tiffany yeah I get you and it's it's it's good right now for me but then you look at the